<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Home of Ish</title>
    <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home of Ish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:28:04 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beatboxerish.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Living Without a Sim</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/sim-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:28:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/sim-card/</guid>
      <description>I keep subjecting myself to interesting conditions and out-of-the-ordinary choices. This time, it was living with an inactive sim card. For a month. A month of my life, which is quite a lot, I lived without a sim card in Goa. Good times!
It was around 1.04.24 when my Airtel sim just stopped showing on my device. It didn&amp;rsquo;t show up and my Iphone 14 threw a &amp;lsquo;No Sim Found&amp;rsquo; error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fieldwork with Coastal Impact-I</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/fieldwork-with-coastal-impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 02:40:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/fieldwork-with-coastal-impact/</guid>
      <description>I have shifted to Goa and by now, have spent some time working with two very interesting NGOs, Technology for Wildlife(TfW) and Coastal Impact (CI). With both of these, I have gotten opportunities to engage in fieldwork. With TfW, the fieldwork is more terrestrial and drone-based while CI offers boat trips and scuba diving. This is probably the first time I have actually got paid to get away from my laptop and do some interesting on-the-ground work (akin to how I once went on a bike ride at Locus as a pillion on one of our delivery partner).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocket man</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/rocketman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 23:42:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/rocketman/</guid>
      <description>Rocket Man starts playing in the background as I am listening to an extremely emotionally overwhelming conversation. We haven&amp;rsquo;t hit the chorus yet. Someone in the group is still talking. This is the first time I attempt to listen to the lyrics of this song. They are sad. Profoundly lonely, floating somewhere around in the ambience of Larder and Folk, these lyrics start making sense. At least to me.
I look for cues to understand if other people are listening to this song too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writings on the Web</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/writings-on-the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 11:36:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/writings-on-the-web/</guid>
      <description>I have been writing on the web since a while. It&amp;rsquo;s out there. Though never took time to collate it all in one specific place. When these writings take place depends on my idea of free time and emotional state at a given point in time. I keep fluctuating between different states of what I think I should be doing with time in general and my writing bears the brunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me@03-2024</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/about-me-03-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:04:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/about-me-03-24/</guid>
      <description>Heyoo!
As I finally find time to focus on things that I like, hobbies, and just life in general, I have also found time to revisit this area of the web. Today falls in 03-2024 and this is a brand-new introduction to my current state of existence ^_^
I have tried so many things! Shifted from being a beatboxer to a research assistant to working at a startup to starting up on my own and finally, to another exciting and very interesting place in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of Hyperlocal Behaviour</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/hyperlocal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 23:33:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/hyperlocal/</guid>
      <description>Life is getting more and more tumultuous. People seem to be converging in their behaviour and likings but at the same time seem to be discovering their own hyperlocal behavioural patterns. With the evolution and proliferation of technology, with tech creeping into every sun-laden crevice, more and more people are crawling out of their chinks out into the open, onto the web, like cockroaches crawling out and getting stuck into a spiders web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dada</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/dada/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 10:50:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/dada/</guid>
      <description>Dada (Hindi for Grandad) Disciplined, a minimalist, extremely supportive, ever loving, the most reliable person ever, flexible and yet a maverick, a stubborn resilient fighter…all of these terms can only help in painting a snippet of what my grandad, dada, meant to me. However, the term I would choose over all these is companion. In fact, I would even argue that he was my companion more than anyone else’s towards the last few years of his life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Open Water Course</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/owc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 19:09:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/owc/</guid>
      <description>This is something that I have yearned for the longest. I have always wanted to dive properly, get certified, and
obtain that freedom to dive wherever I go. A certified Open Water Diver is what I am now. It feels good, amazing, blissful, grateful, extremely lucky, and free. Free from the age long constraints that I have had put on me.
I finally feel that I am free. I finally felt that I was free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bangalore Farewell</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/bangalore-farewell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 01:22:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/bangalore-farewell/</guid>
      <description>I had my official in-office farewell today at Locus. It was a quaint gathering organized by our CHO (let&amp;rsquo;s see if you can find out what this term means). We had a couple of cakes that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t eat (thanks to Bangalore weather caused phlegm), a couple of people that cared about me and a couple people amiss. I gave an underwhelming farewell speech, with a smile on my face grinning eye to eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings@Loneliness</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/musings-1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 16:49:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/musings-1.0/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I have been feeling a little lonely. A little alone in this beautiful city called Bangalore. Down with viral, there&amp;rsquo;s not much that I can do apart from limited eating outside, limited physical activity, and limited social energy.
On any normal day, badminton would be my go-to activity. I would end up exercising, learning a new skill, socializing, and clearing my thoughts. All of these are extremely important needs that I need to give time to whenever and wherever to function productively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 16:23:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hello there&amp;hellip;
As this world become crazier, messier, and increasingly distant, I have decided to find and establish my place in it through this website. It took me a while to finally work a little and create a home for my digital self but thanks to Hugo, someone has a new place for themselves that they might grow to like and call home.
My journey to where I am on 2022-09-25 has been a fun yet tortuous branch of your typical Indian upper middle class trajectory.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
