<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Home of Ish</title>
    <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home of Ish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:35:54 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beatboxerish.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Respect for the Forest</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/respect-for-the-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:35:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/respect-for-the-forest/</guid>
      <description>My views, respect, admiration, and love for the forest reached a different level in Bharatpur, Rajasthan, India on 24th Oct 2022, Monday. This is the day me and my dad got stuck in the national park post its closing time. This is the day when we firsthand felt what it would mean to be alone in a forest post with darkness engulfing you and your phones flashlight being the only thing keeping you from being swallowed in the darkness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings@Loneliness</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/musings-1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 16:49:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/musings-1.0/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I have been feeling a little lonely. A little alone in this beautiful city called Bangalore. Down with viral, there&amp;rsquo;s not much that I can do apart from limited eating outside, limited physical activity, and limited social energy.
On any normal day, badminton would be my go-to activity. I would end up exercising, learning a new skill, socializing, and clearing my thoughts. All of these are extremely important needs that I need to give time to whenever and wherever to function productively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 16:23:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beatboxerish.github.io/posts/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hello there&amp;hellip;
As this world become crazier, messier, and increasingly distant, I have decided to find and establish my place in it through this website. It took me a while to finally work a little and create a home for my digital self but thanks to Hugo, someone has a new place for themselves that they might grow to like and call home.
My journey to where I am on 2022-09-25 has been a fun yet tortuous branch of your typical Indian upper middle class trajectory.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
